<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Moments of Inspiration</title>
    <description>
We have all experienced moments in our life when we feel inspired. These are moments when we feel inspired and feel that life is worth living. Moments, triggered by a piece of music, writing, poetry or a picture, we have an so many sources of inspiration. In this blog I will capture some of my moments of inspiration. In this blog you will find some of my moments of insight; I would love to discover yours.
</description>
    <link>http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 10:35:18 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 10:35:18 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is Music</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;music---the-building-blocks&quot;&gt;Music - The building blocks&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will start by building up an understanding of what music is.
by deconstructing music into its elements and then
build up the structure of music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First let us look at a single &lt;em&gt;tone&lt;/em&gt; in music.
The fundamental components of a single &lt;em&gt;tone&lt;/em&gt; in music are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pitch&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Volume&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Duration&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reverberation&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Timbre&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For groups of notes we can also define:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Scale&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tempo&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Meter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-tone&quot;&gt;The Tone&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have all heard it and said “music is made up of notes”. Later we will get more abstract and talk about music being about “music is about the spaces between the notes”. But first let us understand the notes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In these articles we will make a distinction between &lt;strong&gt;notes&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;tones&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt; a single unit of sound in written music. &lt;strong&gt;Tone&lt;/strong&gt; a single unit of sound  in the music we hear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We introduce notes when we encounter written music; until then we will only refer to tones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;pitch&quot;&gt;Pitch&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everything that we recognize as sound is made up of vibrations. If we pluck a
string on an acoustic instrument the air around it is compressed and decompressed.
These changes in pressure of the air travel through the air to reach our ear and cause the ear drum to vibrate. This vibration is then converted into electrical signals that are carried to the brain which then interprets the signal as a sound!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The brain then recognizes that the tone has a particular pitch and for the trained musician you can even recognize the actual frequency of the tone! Isn’t it amazing to think that all this (and more) happens when I pluck a string and you hear the tone!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before we proceed a definition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Frequency&lt;/strong&gt; The number of vibrations per second that a string makes is called its
frequency. The unit that we use to measure the frequency is called the Hertz (Hz) defined after Heinrich
Hertz who among other things made the first radio transmitter.
So where can we see the use of this definition in music? Every tone has a
frequency. So when we pluck the string of a tuned guitar, the first string (E) vibrates at a frequency of 329.63 Hz. And when we strike a piano, the middle A vibrates at a frequency of 440 Hz.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We cannot hear all the sounds that can be produced.  The human ear is only able to hear sounds that have frequencies in the range 20Hz - 20,000 Hz.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 17:19:03 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/update/music/2016/03/19/TheWayThingsAre.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/update/music/2016/03/19/TheWayThingsAre.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>update</category>
        
        <category>music</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Choices</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Between the stimulus and the response there is a moment, between action and reaction there is a moment, it is in this moment that our entire life is played out. The choices that we make for our responses in those moments define our lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given that this moment is all important, why can’t we just make good choices and be in control of our responses? 
There are many answers to this question. Let us focus on one aspect of this of the answer to this question, the deep biological reasons for our responses. The immediate response that we have especially in stressful/unusual/unplanned situations is governed by the amygdala. This is a primitive part of our human brain that governs our instinctive responses. This part of  the brain was built to react to danger and responds with a “flight or fight” response, which is not optimal. The frontal cortex which is the thinking part of our brain only gets to react a fraction of a second later. We would respond better to situations if we could leverage the frontal cortex of our brain. But we fail to do so because of our biology. So if we want to conquer our responses what can we do, are we helpless? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before we start, let us begin by realizing that controlling our responses is the single most important art that we can try to master. Think of a few things that you could achieve once you have mastery over your self and your responses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are three practical things we can do to improve the way we respond to situations:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Meditation&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Anticipation&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Training&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;meditation&quot;&gt;Meditation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will write more about meditation in another note. It is becoming clear to us that meditation, the art of mindfulness  is an important aspect of our lives and a skill that we must cultivate. As you have experienced there is an “observer” in our minds that seems to watch our actions and thoughts. This is the deeper inner self, that gives each one of us the sense of “I am”. The meditation that I am taking about is taking 5 minutes a day and becoming aware of becoming aware of your self. Observing your thoughts as they arise, and centering your mind back on being aware of yourself.
 
Please try this:
Here is a guided meditation that you can try:&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=422n7tzAxEI&quot;&gt;this guided meditation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can look at articles and talks by Kabat Zinn like this &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3nwwKbM_vJc&quot;&gt;talk at Google: Mindfullness with Jon Kabat-Zinn&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or this one &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xeCXhXDkzpw&quot;&gt;Mindfullness - An Introduction&lt;/a&gt;
After trying this daily for a couple of weeks, I would love to hear your experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;anticipation&quot;&gt;Anticipation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We need to be able to anticipate the situations that we will be put into and think about how we are going to respond. Later we need to reflect on what happened and see how effective our anticipation was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Did the situation arise as we had anticipated?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Did we respond as we planned? If yes, then you need to be very proud of yourself. Otherwise, you need to think about why you responded the way you did.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Did something happen that you did not anticipate?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;training&quot;&gt;Training&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coupled with anticipation, is the notion of training. We need to practice situations that we can face and practice our responses. The simplest optimal response to a stressful/unplanned situation is to say “Let me think about that and get back to you”. This will break the normal sequence and give you time to choose your response. Make the time to think about the situation and choose your response. Be positive, cooperative and constructive in your response.
Once we have chosen this path of action include a reflection on a daily basis to see if your training has resulted the changes in behavior that you need. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Was I in situation that I had been training for? &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Did I respond the way I trained? &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If not why not?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Do I need to add something to my training?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the subject of training, there is a lot more training that we can do, to make sure that when we respond we are responding optimally. We will explore this more in the coming notes.
 
Just by reading this you have started your journey on a path to fulfilling your potential and being a happier person and achieving your goals.  
“A journey of a thousand miles starts with one step…” I hope that you will take these first steps.. I look forward to being part of your journey.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 17:19:03 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/update/2016/03/19/Choices.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/update/2016/03/19/Choices.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Moments of Inspiration</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We have all experienced moments in our life when we feel inspired. These are moments when we feel that life is worth living and we have found another reason for this. These &lt;strong&gt;moments&lt;/strong&gt;, triggered by a piece of music, writing, poetry or a picture are moments that we need to treasure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our lives are so precariously balanced, between the infinities. In space, between the infinity of the largeness of the cosmos and the infinity of the smallness of the subatomic world. In time, between the infinity of the past and the infinity of the future. Now as a scientist, I know that these are not really infinite. We know, for example, the infinity of the past is about 14 billion years and that the infinity of the size of the observable universe is actually 46 billion light-years. In my life I have found great inspiration in understanding these questions. And unravelling the amazing stories of how we have discovered all this. While it is amazing that this self aware and replicating carbon based life form that we can homo-sapiens has been able to comprehend so much it is also true that there are so many “limits” to our understanding. As we uncover the mysteries in all that lies around us, and experience life, we also realize how brief life is. This can be something that is very depressing. We desperately need inspiration in all the different forms that we can find it it in. Inspiration to to keep us going, to find hidden meaning, structure and purpose in everything that surrounds us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this blog I will capture some of my moments of inspiration.
I would love to discover some of your &lt;strong&gt;moments&lt;/strong&gt; of inspiration.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 14:00:28 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/jekyll/update/2016/03/18/FirstPost.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/jekyll/update/2016/03/18/FirstPost.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>WHEN</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHEN&lt;/strong&gt; I have emptied my soul, I am full of life &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;WHEN&lt;/strong&gt; I am most alone, I am connected to all &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;WHEN&lt;/strong&gt; I have faced my biggest fears, I am most calm &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;WHEN&lt;/strong&gt; I recognize my ignorance, I discover deeper knowledge &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;WHEN&lt;/strong&gt;  I have lost my identity, I finally discover who I am &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;WHEN&lt;/strong&gt; I weather the storms of grief, I discover an oasis of tranquility &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;WHEN&lt;/strong&gt; I experience the burning ache of sorrow, I have known the bliss of love &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;WHEN&lt;/strong&gt; I am shrouded by silence, I hear the music I could never hear before &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;WHEN&lt;/strong&gt; I am most wretched, I am touched by grace &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;WHEN&lt;/strong&gt; I have finished my struggles, I will know peace&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2016 13:00:28 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/jekyll/update/2016/02/06/SecondPost.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/jekyll/update/2016/02/06/SecondPost.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
