<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Moments of Inspiration</title>
    <description>
We have all experienced moments in our life when we feel inspired. These are moments when we feel that life is worth living and we have found another reason for that makes it all worthwhile. In this blog you will find some of my moments of insight; I would love to discover yours.
</description>
    <link>http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 09:58:59 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 09:58:59 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Efficiency - Doing things right</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This morning I was watching the NY city marathon, and marveling at the efficiency of the leading marathon runners. Of all the life forms on the planet we the human beings are outstanding running machines. We may not be as fast as cheetah or even a horse, but we can outrun them! Our ability to keep ourselves cool and fuel ourselves by tapping our fat sources is so amazing that we run further that most animals on the planet!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, all this thinking about efficiency lead me to write this note about how we can take inspiration from the dedication to training and efficiency of the marathon runner into all aspects of our lives.
Before we start to do think about efficiency I want to encourage you think about efficiency vs effectiveness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Efficiency is Doing things Right
Effectiveness is Doing the Right things&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today we will focus on efficiency. In the next post we will look at effectiveness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;efficiency&quot;&gt;Efficiency&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How efficient are you in all the activities you pursue? Consider that if you have not spent a lot of time thinking about this, you could easily improve your performance tenfold. (10X your performance.) Think about &lt;strong&gt;why&lt;/strong&gt;  you would want to 10x your performance. Use this to fuel your motivation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;List a few activities that are most important to you. How would you evaluate your efficiency?
Break down the activities into skills and evaluate how efficient you are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example if you are cook here are a skills that you could evaluate to become a better cook.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Knife skills:&lt;/strong&gt; Have you spent time on improving your knife skills?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cooking techniques:&lt;/strong&gt; How good is your Braising, sautéing, frying, baking etc.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluate the tools you use:&lt;/strong&gt; Is your knife sharp? How often do you sharpen your knife? Are you using the right pans? Do they need an upgrade?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are a writer (or programmer): Evaluate different aspects of the activities/skills related to your work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Typing skills:&lt;/strong&gt; Even though we spend a lot of time typing , many of us still use ineffective hunt and peck techniques. We could be some much more efficient if we took a little time to learn to touch type.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organization of materials:&lt;/strong&gt; How do you organize your materials? How streamlined is the organization of your materials. Is it easy for you to find some thing?  Do you have a good system to back up your materials?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Writing and publishing platform:&lt;/strong&gt; If you create content in any form you should look at your end to end process for creating content and see if that if efficient.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you need we can spend some time reviewing an  area that is of interest to you and see if we can come up with some efficiency improvements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you made a list of skill/activities that you can be more efficient in? Remember why you are doing this. Do not lose touch with the WHYs? Make a plan and get started on your journey to a 10x better version of your self.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the next post we will look at Effectiveness. We will also review planning and execution in future posts.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/update/2016/11/06/Efficiency.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/update/2016/11/06/Efficiency.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Unlocking the power of - Why?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why?&lt;/strong&gt; Asking this simple question in different contexts and having the tenacity to keep asking this question until you get a good answer is the key to unlocking your full potential and achieving success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tell me about yourself. Go on… Now reflect on your reply.
Almost always, we tend to hear people tell us &lt;strong&gt;“What they do”&lt;/strong&gt;. There are few who talk about &lt;strong&gt;why&lt;/strong&gt; they do &lt;strong&gt;what&lt;/strong&gt; they do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps you have heard the story of Christopher Wren, one of the greatest of English architects, who walked one day unrecognized among the men who were at work upon the building of St. Paul’s cathedral in London which he had designed. “What are you doing?” he inquired of one of the workmen, and the man replied, “I am cutting a piece of stone.” As he went on he put the same question to another man, and the man replied, “I am earning five shillings twopence a day.” And to a third man he addressed the same inquiry and the man answered, “I am helping Sir Christopher Wren build a beautiful cathedral.” That man had vision. He could see beyond the cutting of the stone, beyond the earning of his daily wage, to the creation of a work of art—the building of a great cathedral. And in your life it is important for you to strive to attain a vision of the larger whole. (Also attributed to Louise Bush-Brown, director of the Pennsylvania School of Horticulture for Women.)&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Christopher_Wren&quot;&gt;Link to wikiquote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can see this person who could talk about the WHY was clear more inspiring to us, and he probably lead a more fulfilled and satisfied life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Things to do:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Take a moment to apply the question WHY? To your life.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Are you someone who always asks this question? Have you given up on asking the question?&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Commit to asking &lt;strong&gt;Why?&lt;/strong&gt; more often in your life.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Apply this question to a few activities in your life. Why am I doing this Project? Why am I learning this subject? Why am I working in this job?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;After a week reflect on the changes that you experience.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Use the WHYs in your communication to others. Tell them about the cathedrals you are building or you want to build in your life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The answers will be difficult and sometimes even seem impossible to find. &lt;strong&gt;Remember&lt;/strong&gt; finding answers to the &lt;strong&gt;WHYs&lt;/strong&gt; in your life is what makes life worth living.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/update/2016/10/25/ThePowerOfWhy.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/update/2016/10/25/ThePowerOfWhy.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mental Models and Reality</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We do not interact with the world directly; instead we interact with reality as reflected by our mental model of the world.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please take a moment to think about this statement. Our instinct is to say this is not true.  How can it be?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me illustrate with an example. I was in a meeting and a co-worker was interrupting the meeting by knocking on the door and insisting on getting our attention.  Even though we tried to ignore her, she was insistent and disruptive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Would you be annoyed in such a situation?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, what if I told you that she had a received an urgent call from the hospital where her baby was sick? And she was trying to get your attention to tell you that she had to leave and give you  some essential information you needed for a meeting before she left?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Would you be annoyed now?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What changed in the world outside that caused you to have a different response?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The situation was a the same, someone was interrupting your meeting. But your mental model was different. Your mental picture of the person who was interrupting the meeting was different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Things to do:
	1) Think of situations where you have felt strong emotions. Now reflect whether you could have changed your response by changing your mental model.
	2) Reflect on whether  you could affect your relationship with yourself and with others by changing your mental model.
Think of how effective it can be to change your mental model and by doing this change your responses to different situations.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/update/2016/10/21/MentalModels.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/update/2016/10/21/MentalModels.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Regrets</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t work too hard, express your feelings, keep in touch with your friends, let yourself be happier and live the life that is true to yourself.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you can do this you will eliminate the top 5 regrets that people have at the end of their lives and you would have crossed another key milestone in the “pursuit of happiness”.
What amazed me was that this sounds so natural and obvious that I imagined we would all be living this way. But a moments reflection was enough for me to discover that like many things in life, sometimes the most simple and obvious things elude us. Like all things that are worth doing this too needs effort - constant, diligent effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some concrete steps that you can take to lead a more fulfilling life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Take some time reflect on your life and see if you currently have any of these regrets.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Make a resolution to incorporate these elements into your life.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Create a plan that actively incorporates these elements into your daily life.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What concrete metrics can you use to measure your progress?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Periodically review how you are doing by evaluating your metrics.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Share your thoughts and experiences with your friends and see if you can help them on their journeys or just be a witness to the progress that they are making.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This post is based on ideas in the book by Bronnie Ware, The Top Five Regrets of the dying. Bronnie was nurse who worked in palliative care and she recorded this list based on her experiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is the list:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I wish I’d had the courage to live a life true to myself, not the life others expected of me.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I wish I hadn’t worked so hard.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I wish I’d had the courage to express my feelings.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I wish I had stayed in touch with my friends.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I wish that I had let myself be happier.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/update/2016/10/19/Regrets.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/update/2016/10/19/Regrets.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why aren&#39;t things the way they should be?</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;why-arent-things-the-way-they-should-be&quot;&gt;Why aren’t things the way they should be?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest challenges that we can face in life is reconciling the difference between the way things are and the way things should be. Often, we are clever enough to visualize the way things should be. This leads to immense frustration with the way things are. I have had to deal with this situation often and I am still dealing with this situation all the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are two techniques that I found effective in dealing with this situation:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“Be the change that you wish to see in the world.” - M. K. Ghandhi&lt;/strong&gt;
This is an extremely challenging response to the situation. Leading by example and living your life/doing things the way they should be done is an extremely good way to channel your frustration. In this way you are concentrating your energies into creating/planning/working on the change that you want to see, rather than giving vent to your frustrations or doing nothing.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“God, grant me the serenity to accept the things I cannot change,
Courage to change the things I can,
And wisdom to know the difference.” - The Serenity Prayer&lt;/strong&gt;
I used to carry these words around with me  and always kept a copy on my desk. It is clear and simple message for how to deal with many situations in your life. Read it and reflect on the wisdom in those lines.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Living life on your own terms, not accepting the status quo and being true to your core values is what makes life worth living. So do not be daunted by the magnitude of the change that needs to happen.
&lt;strong&gt;“A journey of a thousand miles begins with the first step”  - Tao Te Ching&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;things-to-do&quot;&gt;Things to do:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Take the time to think about your life and see if some of the conflict and stress you face is because of the difference between the way things are and the way they should be.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Think about what you could do to become the “change you seek”&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Make a plan and take some active steps to create the change we make your world “the way it should be”&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Continue with your mindfulness practice so you can choose your response in the moment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/update/2016/10/15/ThirdPost.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/update/2016/10/15/ThirdPost.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>WHEN</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHEN&lt;/strong&gt; I have emptied my soul, I am full of life &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;WHEN&lt;/strong&gt; I am most alone, I am connected to all &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;WHEN&lt;/strong&gt; I have faced my biggest fears, I am most calm &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;WHEN&lt;/strong&gt; I recognize my ignorance, I discover deeper knowledge &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;WHEN&lt;/strong&gt;  I have lost my identity, I finally discover who I am &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;WHEN&lt;/strong&gt; I weather the storms of grief, I discover an oasis of tranquility &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;WHEN&lt;/strong&gt; I experience the burning ache of sorrow, I have known the bliss of love &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;WHEN&lt;/strong&gt; I am shrouded by silence, I hear the music I could never hear before &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;WHEN&lt;/strong&gt; I am most wretched, I am touched by grace &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;WHEN&lt;/strong&gt; I have finished my struggles, I will know peace&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 14:00:28 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/jekyll/update/2016/03/19/When.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/jekyll/update/2016/03/19/When.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Choices</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Between the stimulus and the response there is a moment, between action and reaction there is a moment, it is in this moment that our entire life is played out. The choices that we make for our responses in those moments define our lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given that this moment is all important, why can’t we just make good choices and be in control of our responses? 
There are many answers to this question. Let us focus on one aspect of this of the answer to this question, the deep biological reasons for our responses. The immediate response that we have especially in stressful/unusual/unplanned situations is governed by the amygdala. This is a primitive part of our human brain that governs our instinctive responses. This part of  the brain was built to react to danger and responds with a “flight or fight” response, which is not optimal. The frontal cortex which is the thinking part of our brain only gets to react a fraction of a second later. We would respond better to situations if we could leverage the frontal cortex of our brain. But we fail to do so because of our biology. So if we want to conquer our responses what can we do, are we helpless? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before we start, let us begin by realizing that controlling our responses is the single most important art that we can try to master. Think of a few things that you could achieve once you have mastery over your self and your responses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are three practical things we can do to improve the way we respond to situations:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Meditation&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Anticipation&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Training&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;meditation&quot;&gt;Meditation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will write more about meditation in another note. It is becoming clear to us that meditation, the art of mindfulness  is an important aspect of our lives and a skill that we must cultivate. As you have experienced there is an “observer” in our minds that seems to watch our actions and thoughts. This is the deeper inner self, that gives each one of us the sense of “I am”. The meditation that I am taking about is taking 5 minutes a day and becoming aware of becoming aware of your self. Observing your thoughts as they arise, and centering your mind back on being aware of yourself.
 
Please try this:
Here is a guided meditation that you can try:&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=422n7tzAxEI&quot;&gt;this guided meditation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can look at articles and talks by Kabat Zinn like this &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3nwwKbM_vJc&quot;&gt;talk at Google: Mindfullness with Jon Kabat-Zinn&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or this one &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xeCXhXDkzpw&quot;&gt;Mindfullness - An Introduction&lt;/a&gt;
After trying this daily for a couple of weeks, I would love to hear your experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;anticipation&quot;&gt;Anticipation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We need to be able to anticipate the situations that we will be put into and think about how we are going to respond. Later we need to reflect on what happened and see how effective our anticipation was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Did the situation arise as we had anticipated?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Did we respond as we planned? If yes, then you need to be very proud of yourself. Otherwise, you need to think about why you responded the way you did.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Did something happen that you did not anticipate?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;training&quot;&gt;Training&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coupled with anticipation, is the notion of training. We need to practice situations that we can face and practice our responses. The simplest optimal response to a stressful/unplanned situation is to say “Let me think about that and get back to you”. This will break the normal sequence and give you time to choose your response. Make the time to think about the situation and choose your response. Be positive, cooperative and constructive in your response.
Once we have chosen this path of action include a reflection on a daily basis to see if your training has resulted the changes in behavior that you need. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Was I in situation that I had been training for? &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Did I respond the way I trained? &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If not why not?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Do I need to add something to my training?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the subject of training, there is a lot more training that we can do, to make sure that when we respond we are responding optimally. We will explore this more in the coming notes.
 
Just by reading this you have started your journey on a path to fulfilling your potential and being a happier person and achieving your goals.  
“A journey of a thousand miles starts with one step…” I hope that you will take these first steps.. I look forward to being part of your journey.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/update/2016/03/19/Choices.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/update/2016/03/19/Choices.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Moments of Inspiration</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We have all experienced moments in our life when we feel inspired. These are moments when we feel that life is worth living and we have found another reason for this. These &lt;strong&gt;moments&lt;/strong&gt;, triggered by a piece of music, writing, poetry or a picture are moments that we need to treasure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our lives are so precariously balanced, between the infinities. In space, between the infinity of the largeness of the cosmos and the infinity of the smallness of the subatomic world. In time, between the infinity of the past and the infinity of the future. Now as a scientist, I know that these are not really infinite. We know, for example, the infinity of the past is about 14 billion years and that the infinity of the size of the observable universe is actually 46 billion light-years. In my life I have found great inspiration in understanding these questions. And unravelling the amazing stories of how we have discovered all this. While it is amazing that this self aware and replicating carbon based life form that we can homo-sapiens has been able to comprehend so much it is also true that there are so many “limits” to our understanding. As we uncover the mysteries in all that lies around us, and experience life, we also realize how brief life is. This can be something that is very depressing. We desperately need inspiration in all the different forms that we can find it it in. Inspiration to to keep us going, to find hidden meaning, structure and purpose in everything that surrounds us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this blog I will capture some of my moments of inspiration.
I would love to discover some of your &lt;strong&gt;moments&lt;/strong&gt; of inspiration.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 14:00:28 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/jekyll/update/2016/03/18/MomentsOfInspiration.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://csmith111.github.io/moments-of-inspiration/jekyll/update/2016/03/18/MomentsOfInspiration.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
